[{"answer": "No, not for New York.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "If you're sitting here in New York, as we are, is it going to be a huge tub load coming our way?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Yes, he could be.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Was that your experience?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, he's a classic Caudillo of Latin America, a strongman, who was infatuated with Che Guevara and Fidel Castro.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "But how do you think history will judge him?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Yes, Ali, there is a disconnect, isn't there?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "I'll say a few things.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "And the poor getting poorer?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is, when you look at the Dow, you look at the S&P 500, or most major companies, much of their revenue comes from the rest of the world.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "So is that combined an indicator of the strengthening economy?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Oh, for crying out loud do not put your money in the stock market right now.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Kai, if you -- if you have got a bit of cash -- and many Americans don't, but if you do have a bit of cash at the moment, is it a good or a terrible time to invest in the stock market?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you go back to just being consistent with culture, culture is really what makes things change and stick in America.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "How are you going to change the way Americans think about guns?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Our fight isn't against guns.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "That's the realistic goal, right, is what you're trying to do?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "The problem with -- it depends on the kind of --", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Is it time to have just as compelling and controversial advertising relating to gun violence?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Because all you ever hear about is fund-raising, for what purpose, I'm not really sure.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "What I'm interested in now is why you have quit the NRA?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Well, they do, do that in their marksmanship program, which you've got to enroll in one of their marksmanship courses to get that.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Do you think it would change their PR, if nothing else if they really started to take seriously advertising and promoting safe gun use?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Do you think many feel unsettled after Sandy Hook the leadership went so aggressively on the front foot and the result was simply the selling of a lot more weapons?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Well, I guess the assault weapons ban would apply to future sales.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Where are you going to get the money to buy them?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "One would be to enforce the existing laws.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "If I could ask you to say one thing that you felt would be most constructive to making America a less violent country in terms the of gun violence, what would you say?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I think preparation is the key to success and you lay it all out, as you well know, as we describe in the book.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Is preparation in the end the single-most important thing?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Well, we all want that.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "What would you get them to do, these politicians, to try to work better for the cause of America?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, the way that works is when I first went to New York, what I wanted was our players to be focused, enthusiastic about coming to work.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "How does that work?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, that's not an easy thing, but you know, when you're talking about this gun culture, the NFL has strong rules against that.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "How do you get them to understand what discipline is like off the field in their real lives?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I try.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Stage, movies, the Oscars, TV, you're doing all of that, are you, Kristin?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I'm so good, but I was just hoping that this time --", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "HENOWETH: Well, first of all, I'm a woman so I have boobs and I don't really know the big deal.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Do you have any problems with what he did?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "You know, I'd be a liar if I didn't say that it was interesting.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What does it say about America today?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well, it's a classic Mark Burnett production, completely over the top, fabulous costumes, beautiful people.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Doesn't it look good?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "It's good news.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "It's good news, right?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Eight, pretty awful.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "On a scale of 1 to 10, how is my accent?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "They don't use language like that on stage.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "I'm going to play at London, Manchester, Edinburgh so tell me from London to Manchester, how many hours is that?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "I love all of the casts and you have this terrible accident.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Isn't it great?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "I was out for about six to seven minutes and I woke up and they said what happened and they said you fell.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "What did you feel?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "HENOWETH: My brain issues are much better, but it does take some time.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "You've still got repercussions?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Yes, they showed it.", "docId": "130305pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Are they going to show the scenes of what happened?", "qSentId": 705}]